[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "WRB", "JJ", "IN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 35, "question": "Is it time he left the party, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 36, "answer": "Well, I'm not sure how important that is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Colin"], "LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "121026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "What reason would that be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "MD", "IN", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "Well, I think when you have somebody of your own race that you're proud of being president of the United States, I applaud Colin for standing with him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 95, "question": "What is your view now about where we are with the information?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 96, "answer": "This is the time that people should be putting plans together.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 125, "question": "Is it as dire today as it seemed last night?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 126, "answer": "I don't think so, because the storm today, and that's the Twitter universe, that was exactly what I was thinking at that moment in time.", "question_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["last night"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 170, "question": "Was he just being stupid?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 171, "answer": "I think it's probably not true.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Colin Powell"]}, "docId": "121026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "What isn't true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "That it's only because he's black and Colin Powell is liberal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 206, "question": "You actually agree with me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 207, "answer": "I agree with the bottom line.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 210, "question": "Is America a more or less racist country since Barack Obama became president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "DT", "JJR", "CC", "JJR", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 211, "answer": "I think it's not a racist country.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 213, "question": "You actually believe that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 214, "answer": "I can save you a lot of time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "Do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 237, "question": "Is that your belief?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 238, "answer": "For the law, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["39 percent"]}, "docId": "121026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "NN", ",", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "NNP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "CD", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 251, "question": "And when you're running for office, will you stop talking philosophically?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 252, "answer": "The latest poll, \"USA Today\"/Gallup says abortion at 39 percent is the number one issue for women in 12 swing states.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 253, "question": "You surprised by that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 254, "answer": "I'm suspicious of that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 258, "question": "Would you like Romney if he wins to overturn Roe versus Wade as he has threatened to in the past?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 259, "answer": "Well, I don't think it's much of a threat.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Wade"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sununu", "Colin Powell"]}, "docId": "121026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "VBG", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 291, "question": "ORGAN: Why did you do it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 292, "answer": "I think you are doing what you are so testy with Sununu doing to Colin Powell.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "Why call the president of the United States a retard?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "Because it's a synonym for loser.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["United States"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "Says who?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "OK, it's offensive and you're going to come up with 20 different ways to tell me it's offensive.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "``", "NNP", "''", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 351, "question": "You wouldn't use the \"N\" word, would you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "``", "NNP", "''", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 352, "answer": "Not the \"N\" word argument.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "121026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "``", "JJ", ":", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "''", "."], "qSentId": 357, "question": "Why would you allow the word police as you put it to make any exceptions?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 358, "answer": "I should have called my book three books back about \"Guilty: Liberal Victims and Their Assault on America\".", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 371, "question": "Will you continue using the retard word?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 372, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 375, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 376, "answer": "Yes, of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "I'm sure you loved that, didn't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "Yes, it's going to be my exhibit henceforth for both of the groups I want to take the vote away from, young people and women.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "You would take away the female vote, would you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["19th"]}, "docId": "121026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 416, "question": "What is the point?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 417, "answer": "That it was a rash experiment and we should reconsider the 19th Amendment.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 421, "question": "What have I said that's been remotely sexist?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "POS", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 422, "answer": "Calm down.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 467, "question": "Who's going to win the election?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 468, "answer": "I think it's going to be Romney.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 482, "question": "Where do you credit the president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 483, "answer": "I like the drone attacks.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 492, "question": "You in favor of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 493, "answer": "I can't say I'm in favor of the withdrawal since I was against the escalation.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "Who is that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 538, "question": "Why do you press those little buttons?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 539, "answer": "I'm not pressing buttons.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 544, "question": "ORGAN: Do you like being offensive?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 545, "answer": "Please.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 554, "question": "Do you mind that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 555, "answer": "Manifestly not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", ",", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 557, "question": "A gift to be offensive?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 558, "answer": "Well, no, to annoy liberals which isn't very hard, by the way.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 559, "question": "Would you ever date a liberal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 560, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "MD", "RB", "VB", ":", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBP", "CC", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 589, "question": "What was your reaction to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 590, "answer": "Well, the word retard is offensive and should not be -- should not be a symbol for someone who is dumb and shallow.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 610, "question": "Have you ever met him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 611, "answer": "TEPHENS: I have.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 615, "question": "Do you think there's a wider argument that, putting aside the disability, the word retard, the offense it causes to people like yourself, that actually you should just use more respect to the president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", ",", "VBG", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RBR", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 616, "answer": "Of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121026pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 637, "question": "What would you like to say in conclusion?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 638, "answer": "I would like to say thank you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]